zefron.com 2011-12-13

# Privacy Policy « ZAC EFRON | ZEFRON.COM – Your first stop and #1 source for all the latest on Zac Efron!

welcome

Welcome to Charismatic, the most reliable online source for Zac Efron. Here at zefron.com we are always striving to provide fans of all ages with the most accurate and up-to-date news, information, and respectful photos of our favorite actor Zac Efron and have been since 2004. 

rumors

**Rumors last updated October 20th, 2011.**

**Did Zac replace Shia LaBeouf in the upcoming movie _The Necessary Death Of Charlie Countryman_?**  
Producer Albert Berger has confirmed that Zac will now be starring in the movie _The Necessary Death Of Charlie Countryman_ , a role which was previously taken by actor Shia LaBeouf. 

**Is Zac starring in the movie _New Year's Eve_?**  
Zac is playing the role of Paul in the movie _New Year's Eve_ , scheduled for a release on December 9th, 2011 and also starring Robert De Niro and Ashton Kutcher.

fan mail

  * **Zac Efron  
P.O. Box 960  
Avila Beach, CA 93424**

Please be aware that while Zac loves his fans and appreciates all the fanmail he has received, new letters and packages arrive for him every day, and a personal response from Zac is not guaranteed upon writing him a letter or sending him a gift. Instead of sending Zac a present, consider donating to a charity he supports instead, such as the [I'm Too Young For This! Cancer Foundation](http://www.stupidcancer.com/).

| 

Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact me by email at [kathrynsuzie@gmail.com](mailto:kathrynsuzie@gmail.com). 

At www.zefron.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.zefron.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.zefron.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.zefron.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.zefron.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.zefron.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.zefron.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. ww.zefron.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.zefron.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
